<resources
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    tools:ignore="MissingTranslation">
    //Created by DP-Hridayan
    Absolutely necessary to follow this string name format
    <string name="changelog_v6_0_3">\n\n• Fixed the issue which caused per app translations to be broken for aShell You</string>
    <string name="changelog_v6_0_2">\n\n• Adapted Github Actions for release builds.\n\n• What this means for you?\n• All subsequent builds including this will be more secure!</string>
    <string name="changelog_v6_0_1">\n\n• Maintenance update</string>
    <string name="changelog_v6_0_0">\n\n• Added WIRELESS DEBUGGING mode for running ADB commands on both own or other device\n\n• Redesigned homepage for minimal navigation and less cluttery input field screen\n\n• Added Warning feedback when executing commands involving critical system packages\n\n• Added in-app updater. Now you can directly download the latest package without visiting Github repository\n\n• Fixed a lot of bugs</string>
    <string name="changelog_v5_2_1">\n\n• Maintenance update</string>
    <string name="changelog_v5_2_0">\n\n• UI improvements\n\n• Fixed some bugs</string>
    <string name="changelog_v5_1_0">\n\n• Small UI improvements</string>
    <string name="changelog_v5_0_0">\n\n• Huge UI and UX improvements across all sections of the app\n\n• Added ROOT and BASIC shell in addition to Shizuku shell for running commands\n\n• Added option to save output in custom directory\n\n• Fixed a lot of bugs and issues\n\n• Optimised app\'s code for better performance and stability</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_4_0">\n\n• Added vibration for haptic feedback\n\n• Added option to change app language from within the app (for devices running Android 13 and above only and excluding unsupported devices)\n\n• Fixed some crashes and improved crash reporting\n\n• Minor UI improvements</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_3_1">\n\n• Now app catches any crashes and provides the option to report them via email</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_3_0">\n\n• Added option to open saved output directly\n\n• Added option to save whole output or the last command output only\n\n• Fixed crashes</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_2_1">\n\n• Fixed an issue with Sharing text to aShell You where the text did not appear when app was starting fresh\n\n• Fixed minor UI issues</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_2_0">\n\n• Stable release of OTG mode\n\n• Added features like save, share, quick scroll buttons to the OTG mode\n\n• Added info cards for quick information\n\n• Added in app update checker along with the option to auto check for updates\n\n• Minor UI improvements</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_1_0">\n\n• Fixed some issues in OTG adb support\n\n• Updated translations</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_0_3">\n\n• Updated dependencies\n\n• Added more command examples</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_0_2">\n\n• Fixed AMOLED theme not working on devices running Android 11 or below</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_0_1">\n\n• Now you can Pin commands for quick access\n\n • Bug fixes and lot of code optimisations</string>
    <string name="changelog_v4_0_0">\n\n• Now you can directly use commands from the Commands section instead of the need to copy them every time\n\n • Added option to delete all bookmarks\n\n• In search : You can now search in commands summary by clicking a prompt chip\n\n• Added sorting options in Commands templates\n\n• Added option to directly bookmark selected items in Commands section\n\n• Chip Indicator shows connected device(currently only in local ADB mode)\n\n• Fixed bugs causing crashes in devices running Android 11 or below\n\n• Added Turkish translation\n\n• Minor UI improvements\n\n• Lot of other bug fixes</string>
    <string name="changelog_v3_9_1">\n\n• Added total bookmarks count\n\n• Fixed some bugs</string>
    <string name="changelog_v3_9_0">\n\n• Added Search in commands section\n\n• Added option to set default working mode\n\n• Improved animations\n\n• Reworked bookmarks section and added sorting options\n\n• Increased bookmarks limit to 25\n\n• Removed ADB shell launcher shortcut and added Commands launcher shortcut\n\n• Fixed padding issues in button navigation\n\n• Fixed some buttons shape</string>
    <string name="changelog_v3_8_2">\n\n• App uses a more refreshed color palette for material you themeing\n\n• Fixed minor bugs</string>
    <string name="changelog_v3_8_1">\n\n• Fixed some crashes that were introduced in v3.8.0</string>
    <string name="changelog_v3_8_0">\n\n• Added black (amoled) theme\n\n• Added undo button to undo paste\n\n• Added option to disable soft keyboard\n\n• Fixed buttons stretched in some screen sizes\n\n• Fixed bookmarks button not appearing after opening the app\n\n• Renamed Examples section to Commands\n\n• Fixed copy command option not appearing for every command template\n\n• App now uses system font everywhere\n\n• Improved UI handling\n\n• Updated translations</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_7_0">\n\n• Now you can share texts from anywhere on your device to aShell You and run commands directly.\n\n• Now you can share shell output directly without needing to save it !\n\n• A lot of optimisations and UI handling.\n\n• Added Chinese translations.\n\n• Updated translations.
</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_6_0">\n\n• Added option to clear the command input field after an error\n\n• Fixed a bug which caused the app to crash upon pasting from clipboard under certain conditions\n\n• Code optimisations</string>
    <string name="changelog_v3_5_1">\n\n• Fixed some issues with bottom navigation.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_5_0">\n\n• Revamped About section of the app.\n\n• Added launcher shortcuts.\n\n• Fixed navigation menu not showing in button navigation.\n\n• Improved bottom navigation menu visibility on scrolling.\n\n• Added per app language support for aShell You (translations aren\'t completed yet).\n\n• A lot of code optimisations.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_4_0">\n\n• Added a Paste button so that you can copy and paste commands quickly.\n\n• Added Error indicators in the text input field.\n\n• Improved Navigation Bar visibility logic.\n\n• Fixed an issue where switches misbehaves under certain situations.\n\n• Fixed add bookmark icon visibility in various contrast levels.\n\n• A lot of code optimisation. App now opens a lot faster than before.\n\n• App will stay in background and won\'t restart every time you close the app by just pressing the back button or gesture.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_3_0">\n\n• Added bookmarks , history and command suggestions to OTG\n\n• Added maximum bookmarks limit.\n\n• Added option to override maximum bookmarks limit.\n\n• A lot of bug fixes.\n\n• Improved some UI handling.\n\n• A lot of code optimisation.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_2_0">\n\n• A lot of UI related improvements.\n\n• Added chips that indicate current ADB working mode.\n\n• A lot of code optimisation.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_1_0">\n\n• Improvements to ADB OTG after initial release.\n\n• Some UI and logic adjustments to accomodate the new otg feature.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v3_0_0">\n\n• Added ADB THROUGH OTG support.\n\n *** You will be able to run ADB commands on other devices using aShellYou by connecting the other device using an OTG cable ***</string>

    <string name="changelog_v2_0_2">\n\n• Removed unnecessary code and resources.\n\n• Minor UI changes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v2_0_1">\n\n• Removed unnecessary code and resources.\n\n• Minor UI changes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v2_0_0">\n\n• Changed app name to aShell You.\n\n• Added predictive back animations for supporting devices.\n\n• Added confirmation dialog popup before clearing screen.\n\n• Fixed StatusBar elements not properly visible in Light mode.\n\n• App is much more smooth now.\n ~ Reduced app size and optimised code.\n\n• Added themed icon for launchers that support themed icons.\n\n• Minor UI changes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v1_3_0">\n\n• Revamped Settings panel.\n\n• Added Double Tap to instant scroll to top and bottom positions in shell output view.\n\n• Minor UI fixes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v1_2_0">\n\n• Added Settings panel.\n\n• Added option to disable smooth scroll in shell output.\n\n• Fixed major bugs:\n\n  ~  Crash while changing device theme.\n\n  ~  Crash while trying to save large shell output . eg : output of \'pm\' command.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v1_1_1">\n\n• Replaced some deprecated api.\n\n• Minor UI changes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v1_1_0">\n\n• Added Scroll To Top and Scroll To Bottom buttons.\n\n• Added Click keyboard Enter key to Send command.\n\n• Added some commands.\n\n• Updated dependencies to include latest material you library.\n\n• Minor UI changes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v1_0_0">\n\n• Added some more command examples.\n\n• Minor UI changes.\n\n• Changed package name to avoid version confusion with original app.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v0_9_1">\n\n• Added changelogs into the app.\n\n• Added highlighted shell output.\n\n• Minor UI changes.</string>

    <string name="changelog_v0_9_0">\n\n• Added dynamic material theming.\n\n• Revamped whole UI to give a fresh look.</string>

</resources>
